insomniacgames.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Insomniac Games

### PRIVACY POLICY

Insomniac Games, Inc., is committed to maximizing your experience on its website within a trusted environment. This privacy policy explains how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you online. We hope this disclosure will help increase your confidence in the Insomniac Games website and enhance your experience. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to information submitted and collected online at our website. It does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline, or to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link.

_What types of information does Insomniac Games collect and how will it be used?_  
Insomniac Games only collects information on a voluntary basis. The personal information we collect is used exclusively for communication and marketing research purposes. The majority of content on our site is offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. There are a few activities on our site where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary. Those activities include things like signing up for an email newsletter or other online information service we may offer, entering a contest, answering a survey, or contacting us. Visitors who wish to subscribe to the Insomniac Games community will be asked to provide some personal information such as an email address. For example, the submitted email address would then be used to send you, via email, our news updates and to otherwise keep you informed as to what’s going on at Insomniac Games. Surveys are conducted strictly for internal profiling purposes and only keep track of anonymous demographic data (e.g., your age, games played, consoles owned). Our website contains links through which an online visitor can email us. We collect personal information contained in the email for the purpose of responding to a visitor’s questions and/or comments. From time to time, we may post on our website job openings at Insomniac Games and provide an email address to which interested applicants can submit their resume. Although we can assure you that any personal information contained in a resume will be used solely for its intended purpose (i.e., to evaluate the applicant.s qualifications), such information is not subject to this privacy policy.

No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.

_What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to Insomniac Games?_  
If you choose not to submit personally identifiable information when requested, you may not be able to access certain areas of our website and you may considerably limit the services we can provide you. To simply use our site, however, you do not need to give us any personally identifiable information.

_Does Insomniac Games use cookies or other means to collect information?_  
You will know when personally identifiable information is collected because you will be asked to fill out a form. However, we may collect some information about you by using data collection technology, so that it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our website, your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. A “cookie” is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user’s computer. (You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.) We do not use IP addresses or cookies to collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, or to link this information to personally identifiable information already collected about you. This information may be used to make our site more interesting and useful to you. Additionally, we may combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a visitor in order to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, or to protect our service, website or visitors to the website.

_With whom does Insomniac Games share my personally identifiable information?_  
From time to time, we may employ and share your personal information with vendors who use it solely to provide support for the internal operations of our website (e.g., technical support and network delivery). These entities will not use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.

It is our policy not to share, sell or rent your personal information to any company not directly related to the manufacture or publishing of Insomniac Games products. We may disclose your personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes, respond to any claims or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Insomniac Games or the public.

_What is Insomniac Games. policy regarding links to third party sites?_  
You should be aware that while you are on a website operated by us, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and for which we are not responsible. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of these websites meet our high standards, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

_Can I choose how my personal information is used?_  
If you wish to opt-out of participating in our community or any other communication from us, please contact us, at any time, via email at privacy@insomniacgames.com.

_How can I access my personal information?_  
If you wish to review, update, or delete any personal information that we may have collected about you, please contact us via email at privacy[at]insomniacgames.com.

_What safeguards does Insomniac Games use to protect my personally identifiable information?_  
We maintain appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personally identifiable information we collect from all visitors. Personal information collected by us is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and are only accessible by authorized employees. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

_How do I ask a question or file a complaint?_  
If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us via email at privacy[at]insomniacgames.com.

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO THE INSOMNIAC GAMES ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLIC, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FROM TIME TO TIME TO ENSURE YOU ARE AWARE OF THESE CHANGES. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE WILL SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE CHANGES.
